Hello everyone, this is Yuri Noguchi from Equal Room, Emi Ota, and Kihara Sato.
Wow! Interesting!
Today, I'm going to collaborate with an amazing person.
I'm going to collaborate with an amazing person, who I'm sure you all already know!
It's a collaboration!
Wow! I'm so happy!
I'm going to play a bomb, but I'm going to play Terror.
I'm so nervous!
It's going to be big, but I'd like to call you!
Se-no!
Yukirin-san!
Please say hello!
I'm Yuki Kashiwagi, nice to meet you!
That's right, this time we are doing a collaboration project with Yuki Kashiwagi of AKB48's Yuki Kashiwagi's channel, Yukirin World!
Wow! I'm so happy!
I'm watching it so much!
I watch it!
I love the music videos, and I love the music store videos, and I love the dancing!
I love dancing!
I'm a very senior!
I really am!
Thank you!
Kashiwagi-san told me that she is graduating from AKB48.
Yes, she will graduate at the end of April after the graduation concert on March 16th.
I joined in 2006, and it's been 17 years.
What year was 2006?
2004.
Oh no!
I've been in AKB48 since I was 2 years old.
Two years old!
I see!
This is a project I'm going to do with Yukirin-san.
Today, Yukirin will teach us the secret of storytelling!
I'm looking forward to it!
Recently, Ikoraf has been getting more and more opportunities to meet face-to-face with our fans.
Yukirin-san is the queen of handshakes!
The one from a long time ago. A long time ago.
But I've been shaking hands for 17 years.
I was wondering if you could teach me how to interact with fans, or rather, the best way to interact with them.
I've thought hard about it and brought it here.
Thank you very much!
I'd like to ask you in advance what you think are the most important things to remember when dealing with fans at a talk.
We have collected 5 questionnaires in advance, and we will be using them in an announcement quiz format.
We hope to answer them in the form of an announcement quiz!
We're doing it, so are we!
If you're doing it, you'll definitely understand.
If you put it in your own words, I'm sure you'll understand.
I'll do my best!
Well then, let's get on with it!
First of all, here is the first important thing to remember when talking with fans!
No matter how long you've been supporting us, you must always do your best to keep it straight.
This is to be straight and proper. Don't twist.
I think everyone is doing it, probably.
Why is it obvious?
It's pretty obvious.
I might guess.
I guess too, but I can do it by a show of hands.
Then, let's see who guesses for everyone.
I'll go for it.
No matter how long you've been supporting us, 00 is always 00!
Oh, wait. Correct?
No, boo-boo.
But that's the way it's done.
Eh, straight up.
Well, then, no matter how long you've been supporting us, 00 is always 00!
Correct!
That's great!
That's a great answer.
I will always tell you what 00 means.
That's really great.
Yay!
It's important as a human being.
You wrote that since then earlier. You wrote about it earlier since then.
By the way.
No matter how long you have supported us, 00 is always 00!
Why is that?
It's important. It's a child.
No, but important.
I hit it in no time.
That's great.
I've been here for a long time, so there are people who come every time.
When I go, I say thank you or thank you very much.
I have decided to tell them no matter how long our relationship is.
Okay, I'll give one point to Iyori.
I'll take it.
Now, what is important in a talk session with your fans.
Here is the second one.
Do or say 00 to the other person.
Huh?
I didn't know I was supposed to be quizzed during the survey.
I thought I was supposed to talk, but I didn't know it was supposed to be like this.
What?
Even if I don't win in the 00, if it's something like this, I think it's OK,
It's also pretty obvious. It's like the tension I mentioned earlier.
That hole is exquisitely difficult.
Even if I knew it, I wouldn't understand it when I see it. It's difficult.
But it's also a natural part of interacting with people,
Especially when you are talking to someone you have never met before.
But now that we have started this photo shoot, our feelings may be quite similar to this.
The three of you are doing this, and I am trying to do this.
Yes, I'm trying to do this.
Yori-chan, please.
Showing respect and being friendly.
It's not bad. That's pretty much how I feel. Really like that.
Like, I'm going to treat them well.
That kind of thing. It'll show in the fiber.
Kimura-chan, please talk to me.
Talk to them, greet them, and so on.
Ah...
I often hear that the most is not good. What is it? I hear it least often.
Why why why?
Like, I'm going to be sociable, and I'm going to be appropriately sociable.
I don't know. I don't know.
I'm thinking like this now. I'm thinking this.
No, no, no.
He says hello or something.
But it's pretty much like that.
Both of them are like that.
Thinking about the other person a little.
Yes. I'm done.
Then, AmiYuri, please.
Ask for their opinion, or use them as a reference.
You're quick.
It was elementary school.
To the fans.
It's important for sure.
It's important.
The hair and the costumes.
Ah. Maybe it's pretty close.
It's close.
I'm going to do something more simple like that.
Simple?
Yoo-chan, are you going to join us?
Match the personality and tension to the other person,
and to keep the tempo of the conversation up.
I see. I see.
It's very important, but I'm a little far away from it.
What's that?
Good bye.
It's very important, but...
It's really simple.
I made it simple.
Made it simple?
Memories for Miyuri.
I try to match the other person's tastes and image.
I get close to them.
I keep it simple. I'm keeping it simple.
I'm being very determined.
If I did that much, I'd be a dead man.
How far is it? A little far.
I want to get to the beginning.
Yes, that's for sure.
You have to be interested in the person you are talking to,
What are you doing, what are you doing, and so on.
Cu.
Are you daring?
The kanji for interest.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Kamonin.
Like "camonin"?
It means something.
I'm scared.
Did you know?
I'm in a hurry.
I was in a hurry.
I wrote the simpler chart.
You want to write it down?
Okay, okay.
Do the real thing.
Oh, can I?
No!
Create!
Yes, Yori.
You have to be interested in the other person.
and be aware of what you know about the other person.
and try to find common ground
and try to find common ground.
It's very detailed!
It's so important, isn't it?
That's what makes me super worried.
Oh, my God!
Like, to find common ground.
Like we're doing this. Like I'm doing this.
Maybe this is the answer, too.
If you simplify those two things, that's the answer.
Oh, wait a minute.
Chiara?
Yes, well, you have to be interested in the person you're talking to.
Ask questions and do your own research.
What?
I know the letters.
What's that?
Partial point. Partial point.
Asking questions is partially correct.
Oh, wow!
0.5 points.
It's so simple, isn't it?
Very simple
Yes, it is.
Talk to them.
Oh!
Is that okay?
That's right!
It's so simple!
It's true!
So, the correct answer is to be interested in the other person, to listen to what they have to say, and to ask questions.
When you look at it this way
Oh, yes, indeed.
But the position of the circle was not so good.
It was too clean.
But the correct answer is that the two of us were right in what we did.
When something happens that you're interested in...
You think there's only that person in the world, and you have a conversation with him or her.
One on one, when you think he is the only one in the world...
I listen to him or her a lot anyway.
I try to get to know that person.
If you have a long time fan
People who support you.
What do you talk about with them?
I get to know them to a certain extent. You get some information about the person.
I can see what they're doing and that kind of thing.
What they did yesterday.
What they did yesterday, how they got here today.
What they're going to do after this.
Yesterday, today, and tomorrow are things that only happen on that day.
Even if you come back next week, you'll have a different story to tell.
So ask questions like that.
Do you like it when people ask you questions?
It doesn't make you feel bad.
What did you eat today?
"How did you get here?
If they're interested, they'll ask questions.
He's listening.
There's more.
The most important thing to remember when you're talking to your fans.
Here's the third one.
When you're asked to do something you're not good at, ____ is the key.
I should guess once by how everyone else is doing it.
I'd like to know about this.
- Do you know it? Yes!
When someone asks you to do something you don't like, you say you don't want to do it, but the key is momentum.
Wow! You're half right!
You're right about not wanting to do it.
Oh! That's great!
No! No!
But! I won't do this.
I can't do it on the spur of the moment!
No! No! No!
No!
You did it.
That's great! That's great! I'll use it.
No! No! No!
That's so cool!
I don't feel bad about it.
Of course it does.
I didn't find anything real.
It's so good. Very good!
Yes! Yuru-chan
Shame is the point!
Wow! Much closer!
Much closer!
Oh no!
But yes! But that's the feeling.
That's pretty close.
Much closer.
But it's not the same.
I don't know.
Yes! Mairi na ku
Yes! Hey, girl.
You say you don't like it, but the point is to look up at her.
Aah! That's enough!
You're so cute.
I like it when you do that.
No!
Oh, wait a minute.
That's it. That's it.
To push in?
To push?
What do you want me to do?
I'm not good at quizzes.
Do your best.
Yes!
Yes, Yori!
Charm is the point.
Wow, you're so close!
Why are you so close!
What's going on?
What the hell!
charm
Look up at me
Charming.
Put it all together already. Put it all together already.
Put it all together.
Put it all together?
Angle, angle.
You already answered my sister's question.
Wait a minute.
Do your best. - No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Good luck.
It's okay.
It's okay?
He gave it to me.
Okay, Yori.
Cute is the key.
That's right!
Cute!
The correct answer is...
When you're asked to do something you don't like, there's a word for that.
Cute is the key.
Why? Or...
Why do you want me to do that? Like, "Why do you want me to do that?
Then the conversation will drift that way.
I don't know.
What you asked for in the first place, it just goes away.
What?
But I thought it was really nice, even if it was kind of brisk.
I'll use it next time.
I think I'll use it this week.
No!
I've learned so much.
I'll go on to the next one.
I'd like to go to the fourth one.
The important thing about the storytelling session.
The fourth is
Report ____ to ____ who ____ to ____.
Reporting
Difficult to ____.Difficult
London.
I'm really sorry, I thought this was going to be a quiz.
I'm getting more and more twisted.
Oh, so it's twisted then.
Not words and stuff.
I'm having so much fun moderating this.
I've decided where the problem is.
I'm looking like a total pompous ass.
I'm going to quiz myself with all these cute girls.
Here you go!
Yes, Iori!
For those who are not good at talking
I report on my daily life.
What do you think?
I think that's a "yes".
All correct answers.
Ehhhhh!
Oh my God!
Wow!
All correct!
It's almost the same when you read it.
The correct answer is that if someone doesn't seem to be very good at talking
I'll tell them what I want them to hear.
Really?
Quizzes are for everyone.
Is that even possible?
Do you do that? Usually.
If I get a "X".
I say, "I made a mess the other day.
That's great.
You're right.
Einyan wrote a lot, too.
But you were right about the funny parts.
That's true.
But you were right about the right things.
Was I right?
You sound young. youthful
Good.
Hiyo-chan, one time.
I'll tell you a story.
What do you mean, "a bunch of times"?
It's true, but Hiyo-chan was right.
There are those who talk a lot.
But there's also a pattern where we don't talk at all.
Like, "What did you eat today?
Or something that made you happy before.
So that the other person only has to respond with a few words.
I'll paraphrase what he says so that he only has to say a few words.
It turned out to be a great success!
That's great.
That's the last one.
Fifth one is this.
When you're low on energy and food, you have to do the "kill move.
It's a little bit different from what I've done in the past, but...
I've been doing handshakes and one-man shows.
I've come up with my own special technique.
Do you do it when you're face to face with a one-man show?
Yes, it's what I do.
By doing this
I'm getting weaker and weaker, and after the second half of the show.
I don't want them to notice that I'm getting weaker.
It's like a special technique to keep them from noticing.
3 points for the left guki yori-san!
Yukiyara on the left: 0.5 points
Yukiyara-san on the left, 0.5 points
Yukiyara-san 0.5 points
Two people ask Yori-chan for a favor.
If Yori-chan says yes, let's make the last problem
Let's make it 10 points.
That's great!
It's up to Yori-chan
She's cute, after all.
Yori-chan
Ten points. 10 points
Yorichan...
Oh no!
You're a genius.
It's good.
But this is pretty much the one I want everyone to know about.
That was the fifth most important one.
That one, of course.
When I started to lose a little energy in the second half...
Yukari.
It's just you.
Just you.
It's a special move.
My...
Talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk.
They'll tell you.
Maybe I can do it.
I'll do it.
I know you.
I know my tricks.
She says she's tired.
Sometimes he asks me nicely.
I don't let him say that.
When he does this, he doesn't tell me.
Yoriyori.
When I'm a little weak in the second half of the day...
A good laugh is a must
A little closer
Hold it.
Oh no, oh no, oh no
High school was like that
I was positive
When it comes down...
I'd jump.
You're not strong enough.
Thank you.
You'll never be heard from again.
Here you go, guys. Yes, guys.
If you're feeling a little low on energy in the second half of the game.
I'm going to play catchphrase.
I see.
Anyway...
Catchphrase.
If you don't do it, you'll forget it.
It's hard when you don't have the strength.
I think I'll do it the other way around.
Everyone looks at each other.
"It's so hard!
It's hard.
Why is that?
I've been hit.
I don't understand.
You're putting me in a bad mood.
You put me in a bad mood.
You mean you're in a bad mood?
Yes, it's like that.
Really.
I don't know.
Raising your voice is a special move.
You're right.
Good for you.
That's great.
In the end...
You have to keep your voice up. That's the secret.
It's hard.
I see.
It's a lot of work.
It takes a lot of energy.
And the rest is pretty rough, too.
Even if it's this face.
And the person talking like this...
Oh, really? That's amazing.
Just by raising your voice.
I'm really interested. I'm really interested.
This one's pretty gradual, too.
Even if I don't move.
Oh, really, that's so great!
Once I say it here...
Five more seconds.
If you raise your voice...
I feel like I'm having a lot of fun.
It makes me feel like I'm on a roll.
If you really can't help it
Please try it!
It's really bad.
So that's it.
I've finished the five presentations.
How about the final point?
Final point
Kiyoka Saito
0.5 points
Niyuri Ota
Yori Miyaguchi
33 points
Eh, 13 points
13 points
Yori Miyaguchi is the winner!
Is there such a thing as a winner?
I learned a lot!
If you find something you can use
Please try to use it!
That's all for now.
This time, Ms. Yukirii came to talk to us about
to teach us the secrets of storytelling
I will do my best next time.
I'll do my best next time.
You'll be fine as you are. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
We'll be on your channel, too.
We'll appear on your channel.
We'll be collaborating with you.
I'd love it if you could watch
I'd be happy to show it to you as well.
Thank you very much.
Oh...
I'm sorry.